Oliver White

+61-407-493-332 || okwhite@pm.me

Nostr: npub1q7why7lw8kq9ufr43ps75ngz3vhx5duqt7xmgklcq3dljqqfjegq2km2vr Resume: https://bit.ly/3P1PaXZ



Twitter || Keybase || Nostr

EXPERIENCE

theschoolofbitcoin.com - Speaker

Speaker regarding the beneficial aspects of Bitcoin, Nodes, Self-Hosting and being a Sovereign Individual.

Deevnation.io - Speaker and Educator

Instructed several classes on Bitcoin Node + Lightning setup and installation.

theschoolofbitcoin.com - Discord Admin (2022 - Now)

An open project to build a dynamic consensus driven curriculum specifically for (de)financial literacy that has the ability to plug into any institution to support learners on problem and project based learning journeys.

kadena.io - Community Manager (2021 - Now)

Kadena was founded on the idea that blockchain could revolutionize how the world interacts and transacts. But to get to mass adoption, chain technology and the ecosystem connecting it to the business world needed to be reimagined from the ground up. Our founders built a proprietary chain architecture and created the tools to make blockchain work for business – at speed, scale, and energy efficiency previously thought unachievable.

Contributions: https://babening.io/

handshake.org - Director Aus Relations (2020 - Now)

Handshake is a decentralized, permissionless naming protocol where every peer is validating and in charge of managing the root DNS naming zone with the goal of creating an alternative to existing Certificate Authorities and naming systems. Names on the internet (top level domains, social networking handles, etc.) ultimately rely upon centralized actors with full control over a system which are relied upon to be honest, as they are vulnerable to hacking, censorship, and corruption. Handshake aims to experiment with new ways the internet can be more secure, resilient, and socially useful with a peer-to-peer system validated by the network's participants.

Contributions: https://learn.namebase.io/about-handshake/mining-hns

Insights and Ideas - Technical Consultant (2008 -2020)

Network design and Infrastructure. Website Development and Management Social Media Manager

JWT Advertising - Network Engineer (2007 - 2008)

Network design and infrastructure. Spent time abroad in Thailand with JWT Advertising, configuring routers and general helpdesk support.

RapidNet - Helpdesk Support (2000 - 2006)

ABOUT

I am a Cisco Network Engineer, a Blockchain expert and a Community Manager with a passion for all things decentralised. I speak multiple languages fluently, and am passionate about Bitcoin, education, virtual reality, and technology as a whole.

EXPERTISE

Fluent in Japanese to University level Proficient with Discord Server management Extremely Quick learner

QUALIFICATIONS

KUMON Japanese Language Cert Cisco Certified Network Professional (CCNA) Microsoft MSITP Wesley College, Swinburne High (VCE) Bradbury School Hong Kong St. Mary's School Tokyo, Japan. Client support to access ISP's external network, such as newsgroups, email, www.